nine timu products that should not exist
or should they starting with this lamp
that can literally shape how the
heck does this thing work next is a
magic wand that works because of a
special piece of paper which ignites
quickly and burns fast next I'm
performing the famous sword swallowing
magic trick which I can only do because
the sword B these are the viral teu
dreads which for some reason all of you
guys think I use for my hair this hat
looks innocent but has a secret water
compartment which you can use to spit at
people this is a real life invisibility
Shield which works because of material
called lenticular lens that can
literally bend light this is edible
money that honestly tastes terrible